<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DaChengPly</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/</link><description>Recent content on DaChengPly</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.dachengply.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Commercial Plywood</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/commercial-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/commercial-plywood/</guid><description>Description Commercial Plywood is a type of plywood can resist moisture and humidity to a certain extent but it cannot be called &amp;lsquo;waterproof&amp;rsquo;. It can withstand some amount of moisture, dampness and humidity, so commercial plywood is most commonly used in the making of home and office furniture, and interior decoration work such as paneling, kitchen cabinet, the trim of car, packing, sofa inside, photo frame back, baby carrier and crib decoration embossed panel and so on.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/contact/</guid><description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our blog?
Please feel free to contact us.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/faq/</guid><description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description></item><item><title>Film faced plywood(Marine Plywood)</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/marine-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/marine-plywood/</guid><description>Description Marine Plywood is a premium grade plywood made from various wood species. It has a sanded face and back and is made with A bond glue which makes it waterproof. Marine ply is perfectly suited to boat and marine related applications. Suitable Applications are boats, docks, high moisture areas and high quality aesthetic purposes. Features:
Light weight, better be used in high building and bridge construction, high strength and good toughness.</description></item><item><title>Melamine MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/melamine-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/melamine-mdf/</guid><description>Information Melamine MDF stands for melamine medium density fiberboard similar with MFC is also extensively used in the fields of office furniture, panel cabinets, wardrobe, interior decoration, etc.
Beside,we have moisture-resistant green color core MDF which is recommended for use in wet area such as bathroom,kitchen. Currently we have available more than 2000 kinds of different colors and designs. All of our wood grain colors are like real wood. Product Information Size&amp;amp;Thickness (4&amp;rsquo;x8&amp;rsquo;)1220x2440x(1.</description></item><item><title>Melamine Plywood</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/melamine-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/melamine-plywood/</guid><description>Features High bending strength. Strong nail holing. Moisture resistant and easy work. Tight construction and high strength. No ratten or decay. Low formaldehyde emission. Suitable for indoor furniture &amp;amp; floor or decoration use. Suitable for indoor construction of viaduct and tall frame building. More than 300 different colors and designs are available. Product Information Size: 1220x2440mm, 1250x2500mm, 910x2150mm Thickness: 1.8-30mm Core: Finger Jointed &amp;amp; Fresh Material: Full Poplar, Full Eucalyptus, Combi, Hardwood, etc.</description></item><item><title>MELAMINE SLOTTED MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/slotted-melamine-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/slotted-melamine-mdf/</guid><description>
Information Slotted MDF panel is used mainly for display board in retail stores and supermarket. It is also can be used for furniture making and wall decoration such as shopfitting, display rack, storage cabinet and etc. Product Information Size 1220x2440mm(4&amp;rsquo;x8&amp;rsquo;),1220x1220mm(4&amp;rsquo;x4') Thickness: 15-25mm Melamine color: Plain and wood grain colors Accessories: Aluminum tape (0.4-1 mm thickness), PVC tape, hooks Groove type: Rectangle, ellipse, trapezoid Groove No.: 7~21 grooves Groove Distance: 75mm / 100mm / 150mm / 200mm/300mm Groove Direction: 1220mm direction or 2440mm direction Usag: Wall decoration Supermarket shelf etc</description></item><item><title>Particle BoardF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/particle-board/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/particle-board/</guid><description>Description Particle board or particle chipboard. When environment protection becomes the mainstream of development, have recycling of residual branches and leaves from the nature, which integrated it into the good quality of particle board that becomes a nature civilization. It reduces the impact on human health which brings us a harmonious and tranquil life. It will have the recycled economy accumulation and extending.
MFC stands for melamine faced chipboard which belongs to melamine artificial board.</description></item><item><title>Plain MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/mdf/</guid><description>Information The medium density board (MDF) is fully called density fiberboard. It is a board made of wood fiber or other plant fiber as raw materials, prepared by fiber, applied with synthetic resin, and pressed under the conditions of heating and pressure.
It has the advantages of uniform texture, smooth surface, compact structure, high strength, heat insulation, sound insulation, difficult deformation, and is easy to process and can be used for carving, painting and veneering.</description></item><item><title>PVC Edge Banding</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/particle-board-copy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/particle-board-copy/</guid><description>Description Usage: sealing four sides of melamine board to make it beautiful and waterproof
Product Information |Thickness:|0.4-3 mm| |Width:|15-70mm| |Color:| More than 500 or as requested| |Surface Finishing:| High glossy, Smooth, Matt and different embossed| |Length Per Roll:| 100m/roll, 200m/roll,300m/roll| |Usage:|Furniture|</description></item><item><title>VENEER FACED MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/veneer-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/veneer-mdf/</guid><description>
Information Size 1220x2440mm,1220x2745mm Thickness: 2.5-25mm Material: Poplar,Pine Core: Pine, Poplar Glue: TSCA, P2 ,E0, E1, E2 Density: 680-730-880kgs/m³ Usage: Furniture, Decoration, etc</description></item></channel></rss>