<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>building materials on DaChengPly</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/categories/building-materials/</link><description>Recent content in building materials on DaChengPly</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.dachengply.com/categories/building-materials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Melamine MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/melamine-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/melamine-mdf/</guid><description>Information: Melamine MDF stands for melamine medium density fiberboard similar with MFC is also extensively used in the fields of office furniture, panel cabinets, wardrobe, interior decoration, etc.
Beside,we have moisture-resistant green color core MDF which is recommended for use in wet area such as bathroom,kitchen. Currently we have available more than 2000 kinds of different colors and designs. All of our wood grain colors are like real wood. Product Information: Size&amp;amp;Thickness (4&amp;rsquo;x8&amp;rsquo;)1220x2440x(1.</description></item><item><title>MELAMINE SLOTTED MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/slotted-melamine-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/slotted-melamine-mdf/</guid><description>
Information Slotted MDF panel is used mainly for display board in retail stores and supermarket. It is also can be used for furniture making and wall decoration such as shopfitting, display rack, storage cabinet and etc. Product Information Size 1220x2440mm(4&amp;rsquo;x8&amp;rsquo;),1220x1220mm(4&amp;rsquo;x4') Thickness 15-25mm Melamine color Plain and wood grain colors Accessories Aluminum tape (0.4-1 mm thickness), PVC tape, hooks Groove type Rectangle, ellipse, trapezoid Groove No. 7~21 grooves Groove Distance 75mm / 100mm / 150mm / 200mm/300mm Groove Direction 1220mm direction or 2440mm direction Usag Wall decoration Supermarket shelf etc</description></item><item><title>Plain MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/mdf/</guid><description>Information The medium density board (MDF) is fully called density fiberboard. It is a board made of wood fiber or other plant fiber as raw materials, prepared by fiber, applied with synthetic resin, and pressed under the conditions of heating and pressure.
It has the advantages of uniform texture, smooth surface, compact structure, high strength, heat insulation, sound insulation, difficult deformation, and is easy to process and can be used for carving, painting and veneering.</description></item><item><title>VENEER FACED MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/veneer-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/veneer-mdf/</guid><description>
Information Size 1220x2440mm,1220x2745mm Thickness 2.5-25mm Material Poplar,Pine Core Pine, Poplar Glue TSCA, P2 ,E0, E1, E2 Density 680-730-880kgs/m³ Usage Furniture, Decoration, etc</description></item></channel></rss>