<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>plywood on DaChengPly</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/tags/plywood/</link><description>Recent content in plywood on DaChengPly</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.dachengply.com/tags/plywood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Commercial Plywood</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/commercial-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/commercial-plywood/</guid><description>Description Commercial Plywood is a type of plywood can resist moisture and humidity to a certain extent but it cannot be called &amp;lsquo;waterproof&amp;rsquo;. It can withstand some amount of moisture, dampness and humidity, so commercial plywood is most commonly used in the making of home and office furniture, and interior decoration work such as paneling, kitchen cabinet, the trim of car, packing, sofa inside, photo frame back, baby carrier and crib decoration embossed panel and so on.</description></item><item><title>Film faced plywood(Marine Plywood)</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/marine-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/marine-plywood/</guid><description>Description Marine Plywood is a premium grade plywood made from various wood species. It has a sanded face and back and is made with A bond glue which makes it waterproof. Marine ply is perfectly suited to boat and marine related applications. Suitable Applications are boats, docks, high moisture areas and high quality aesthetic purposes. Features:
Light weight, better be used in high building and bridge construction, high strength and good toughness.</description></item><item><title>Melamine Plywood</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/melamine-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/blog/1/01/01/melamine-plywood/</guid><description>Features High bending strength. Strong nail holing. Moisture resistant and easy work. Tight construction and high strength. No ratten or decay. Low formaldehyde emission. Suitable for indoor furniture &amp;amp; floor or decoration use. Suitable for indoor construction of viaduct and tall frame building. More than 300 different colors and designs are available. Product Information Size: 1220x2440mm, 1250x2500mm, 910x2150mm Thickness: 1.8-30mm Core: Finger Jointed &amp;amp; Fresh Material: Full Poplar, Full Eucalyptus, Combi, Hardwood, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>