<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Products on DaChengPly</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/products/</link><description>Recent content in Products on DaChengPly</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.dachengply.com/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Commercial Plywood</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/commercial-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/commercial-plywood/</guid><description>Description Commercial Plywood is a type of plywood can resist moisture and humidity to a certain extent but it cannot be called &amp;lsquo;waterproof&amp;rsquo;. It can withstand some amount of moisture, dampness and humidity, so commercial plywood is most commonly used in the making of home and office furniture, and interior decoration work such as paneling, kitchen cabinet, the trim of car, packing, sofa inside, photo frame back, baby carrier and crib decoration embossed panel and so on.</description></item><item><title>Film faced plywood(Marine Plywood)</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/marine-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/marine-plywood/</guid><description>Description Marine Plywood is a premium grade plywood made from various wood species. It has a sanded face and back and is made with A bond glue which makes it waterproof.</description></item><item><title>Melamine MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/melamine-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/melamine-mdf/</guid><description>Description Melamine MDF stands for melamine medium density fiberboard similar with MFC is also extensively used in the fields of office furniture, panel cabinets, wardrobe, interior decoration, etc.
Beside,we have moisture-resistant green color core MDF which is recommended for use in wet area such as bathroom,kitchen.</description></item><item><title>Melamine Plywood</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/melamine-plywood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/melamine-plywood/</guid><description>Features High bending strength. Strong nail holing. Moisture resistant and easy work. Tight construction and high strength. No ratten or decay. Low formaldehyde emission. Suitable for indoor furniture &amp;amp; floor or decoration use.</description></item><item><title>MELAMINE SLOTTED MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/slotted-melamine-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/slotted-melamine-mdf/</guid><description>Description Slotted MDF panel is used mainly for display board in retail stores and supermarket. It is also can be used for furniture making and wall decoration such as shopfitting, display rack, storage cabinet and etc.</description></item><item><title>Particle Board</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/particle-board/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/particle-board/</guid><description>Description Particle board or particle chipboard. When environment protection becomes the mainstream of development, have recycling of residual branches and leaves from the nature, which integrated it into the good quality of particle board that becomes a nature civilization.</description></item><item><title>Plain MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/plain-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/plain-mdf/</guid><description>Description The medium density board (MDF) is fully called density fiberboard. It is a board made of wood fiber or other plant fiber as raw materials, prepared by fiber, applied with synthetic resin, and pressed under the conditions of heating and pressure.</description></item><item><title>PVC Edge Banding</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/pvc-edge-banding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/pvc-edge-banding/</guid><description>
Description Usage: sealing four sides of melamine board to make it beautiful and waterproof
Product Information Thickness: 0.4-3 mm Width: 15-70mm Color: More than 500 or as requested Surface Finishing: High glossy, Smooth, Matt and different embossed Length Per Roll: 100m/roll, 200m/roll,300m/roll Usage: Furniture</description></item><item><title>VENEER FACED MDF</title><link>https://www.dachengply.com/veneer-mdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dachengply.com/veneer-mdf/</guid><description>
IDescription Product Information Size 1220x2440mm,1220x2745mm Thickness: 2.5-25mm Material: Poplar,Pine Core: Pine, Poplar Glue: TSCA, P2 ,E0, E1, E2 Density: 680-730-880kgs/m³ Usage: Furniture, Decoration, etc</description></item></channel></rss>